KAMEYU
TRANSACTION NO. BANK NO.
BRANCH NO. WINDOW NO.
DEPOSIT AMOUNT BALANCE
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 18
SHIGECHI'S HARVEST, PART 1
BOOM
HARVEST
THE PARK IS FOR POLITE CHILDREN
WHO GET ALONG WITH OTHERS
MORIOH CITY
KAMEYU
PRODUCT VOUCHER
20 YEN
MEIWADO STATIONERY
OSCAR
NAGASAKI CLEANERS
YOTSUBA ELECTRONICS
SERVICE CARD
RUMBLE
GRAB
EXCITING
WINNING NUMBERS
SG GROUP
PAYOUT PERIOD
FROM 1/20/1999
TO 6/21/1999
3RD
SG GROUP
BT GROUP
PAYOUT PERIOD
FROM 1/20/1999
TO 6/21/1999
WINNING NUMBERS
LIST
PRIZE 5 MILLION YEN
5 MILLION YEN
EPISODE 19
SHIGECHI'S HARVEST, PART 2